Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 78 RPM Records, circa 1903-1959; 2734 sound discs
  - Side A: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Boolavogue" [CAL.134] Side B: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Wind That Shakes the Barley" [CAL.135] (Regal Zonophone I.Z. 834) (Disk XA78 261)
  - Side A: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Broken Song" [CAL.307] Side B: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Bard of Armagh" [CAL.309] (Regal Zonophone I.Z. 1225) (Disk XA78 262)
  - Side A: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Irish Brigade" [CAL.304] Side B: O'Shaughnessy, Cecil, "Fenian Men" [CAL.310] (Regal Zonophone I.Z. 1227) (Disk XA78 263)
  - Side A: O'Siochain, Sean, "Rose of Mooncoin" [OEL.245] Side B: O'Siochain, Sean, "Patsy McCann" [OEL.225] (His Master's Voice I.M. 953) (Disk XA78 264)
  - Side A: O'Siochain, Sean, "South Down Militia" [OEL.236] Side B: O'Siochain, Sean, "Nation Once Again" [OEL.237] (His Master's Voice I.M. 954) (Disk XA78 265)
  - Side A: O'Siochain, Sean, "Flower of Finea" [OEL.314] Side B: O'Siochain, Sean, "Bringing Home the Turf" [OEL.315] (His Master's Voice I.M. 993) (Disk XA78 268)
  - Side A: Osiothchain, Sean, "Goat's Will" [CAL.253] Side B: Osiothchain, Sean, "Bold Thady Quill" [CAL.255] (Regal Zonophone I.Z. 1082) (Disk XA78 266)
  - Side A: Osiothchain, Sean, "Wife of the Bold Tenant Farmer" [CAL.254] Side B: Osiothchain, Sean, "Banks of Sillawn" [CAL.257] (Regal Zonophone I.Z. 1119) (Disk XA78 267)
  - Side A: Osiothchain, Sean, "Ball in the Bro" [OEL.224] Side B: Osiothchain, Sean, "Jimmy Murphy" [OEL.228] (His Master's Voice I.M. 955) (Disk XA78 269)
  - Side A: Osiothohain, Sean, "Step Together" [CAL.252] Side B: Osiothohain, Sean, "Follow Me Up to Carlow" [OEA.256] (Regal Zonophone IZ.1095) (Disk XA78 270)
  - Side A: Ossman, Vess L., "Bit o' Blarney " [Matrix # not listed] (Standard 3289) One-Sided (Disk XA78 292)
  - Side A: Ossman, Vess, "Whip and Spur" [4395] Side B: Lufsky, Marshall P., "Little Sweetheart" [4377] (United A826) (Disk XA78 2356)
  - Side A: O'Toole, Dennis, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McHugh, Martin, "Killarney" [Matrix # not listed] (National Music Lovers of New York 1081) (Disk XA78 271)
  - Side A: O'Toole, Knuckles, "Sweet Rosie O'Grady" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: O'Toole, Knuckles, "Give My Regards to Broadway" [Matrix # not listed] (Waldorf BR-61) (Disk XA78 272)
  - Side A: O'Toole, Knuckles, "There Is a Tavern in the Town" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: O'Toole, Knuckles, "Wait 'Til the Sun Shines, Nellie" [Matrix # not listed] (Waldorf BR-78) (Disk XA78 273)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's "Pride of Erin" Orchestra, "Kitty Malloy's Favorite" [38897] Side B: Paddy Killoran's "Pride of Erin" Orchestra, "Galway Bay" [38898] (Decca 12003), 1934 (Disk XA78 1423)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's "Pride of Erin" Orchestra, "Girls of Brainbridge" [38891] Side B: Paddy Killoran's "Pride of Erin" Orchestra, "Dublin Lassies" [38892] (Decca F.5355) (Disk XA78 1970)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "Come Back Paddy Reilly to Ballyjames Duff'" [62248] Side B: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "O'Donnel" [62249] (Decca 12124) (Disk XA78 24)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "My Little Colleen" [62244] Side B: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "River Shannon" [62245] (Decca 12113) (Disk XA78 45)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "Little Dash of Dublin" [62243] Side B: Paddy Killoran's Irish and American Serenaders, "Teddy O'Neil" [62250] (Decca 12116) (Disk XA78 46)
  - Paddy Killoran's "Pride of Erin" Orchestra, "Sweeps - Heirloom", undated (Box 11, Box 3)
  - Side A: Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Dublin Reels" [10-983] Side B: Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Patrick's Jigs" [10-984] (Standard F-14017) (Disk XA78 34)
  - Side A: Pastor, Tony, "Sioux City Sue" [6055] Side B: Pastor, Tony, "Loop- De- Loo" [6056] (Cosmo 471) (Disk XA78 291)
  - Side A: Pat Fallon's Country Leitrim Ceilidhe Band, "Wind That Shakes the Barley" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Pat Fallon's Country Leitrim Ceilidhe Band, "Devil's Dream" [Matrix # not listed] (Celtic CI 1038) (Disk XA78 699)
  - Side A: Pat Fallon's Country Leitrim Ceilidhe Band, "Corry Boys – Reel" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Pat Fallon's Country Leitrim Ceilidhe Band, "St. Patrick's Day – Jig" [Matrix # not listed] (Celtic CI 1037) (Disk XA78 1207)
  - Side A: Pat Roche's Harp and Shamrock Orchestra, "Boys of Blue Hill" [C 9384] Side B: Pat Roche's Harp and Shamrock Orchestra, "Molly Durkin" [C 9385] (Decca 12007) (Disk XA78 389)
  - Pat Roche's Harp & Shamrock Orchestra, "Green Mountain Longford Maid", undated (Box 10, Box 8)
  - Side A: Pat Roche's Harp and Shamrock Orchestra, "St. Patrick's Day" [C-90488] Side B: Pat Roche's Harp and Shamrock Orchestra, "Job of Journey Work" [C-90449] (Decca 12061) (Disk XA78 390)
  - Side A: Patrick Stanton's Orchestra, "Bagpipe Orchestra" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Label Missing, "Label Missing" [Label Missing] (Robinson Catolog # not listed) Non-commercial (Disk XA78 443)
  - Side A: Patti, Adelina, "Martha" [Matrix # not listed] (His Master's Voice 31869) One-Sided 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2282)
  - Side A: Patti, Mme. Adelina, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 88117) One-Sided 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2272)
  - Side A: Pavloska, Irene, "Love's Old Sweet Song" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Pavloska, Irene, "Just A 'Wearyin for You" [Matrix # not listed] (Brunswick 13003) (Disk XA78 300)
  - Side A: Payne, Jack, "Medley of Irish Airs Part I" [17591] Side B: Payne, Jack, "Medley of Irish Airs Part II" [17592] (Melotone 6.3.07) (Disk XA78 301)
  - Side A: Peaner, Mr. C, "Irish Jig" [One-sided]" (Nicole 386) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2664)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "There's a Typical Tipperary Over There" [79061] Side B: Harrison, Charles, "That Old Irish Mother of Mine" [79085] (Columbia A2937) (Disk XA78 304)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Fast Asleep in Poppyland" [12] Side B: Fields, Arthur, "I Might Be Your Once in a While" [20] (Pathé 22214) (Disk XA78 305)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Let's Go Back to Baby Days" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Miss Jones and Mr. Spencer, "How Kathleen Proposed" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 16341) (Disk XA78 306)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "While They Were Dancing Around" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Peerless Quartet, "Irish Tango" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17571) (Disk XA78 307)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Hong Kong" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Campbell, Albert and Henry Burr, "Lookout Mountain" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18295) (Disk XA78 308)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "What a Friend We Have in Mother" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Burr, Henry, "That Old Fashioned Mother of Mine" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19305) (Disk XA78 309)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Moonlight on the Lake" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Victor Minstrels No.10, "Victor Minstrels No. 10" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 16149) (Disk XA78 312)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Negro Wedding in Southern Georgia" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Harlan, Byron G., "School Days" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 16526) (Disk XA78 313)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Take Me Back to Alabam'" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Wright, Horace accompanied by Louise and Ferera, "O'Brien is Tryin' to Learn to Talk Hawaiian" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18167) (Disk XA78 314)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Sweet Genevieve" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Bauer, Franklyn, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 20283) (Disk XA78 319)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Where is My Boy To-Night" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Peerless Quartet, "When the Roll is Called Up Yonder" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 22945) (Disk XA78 320)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "When I'm Gone You'll Soon Forget" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Burr, Henry and Frank Croxton, "Weeping Willow Lane" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19870) (Disk XA78 1229)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Medley of Foster Songs" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Victor Minstrel Company, "Virginia Minstrels" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 35095) 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2283)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet with Billy Murray, "My Dream of the Big Parade" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Burr, Henry, "Prisoner's Sweetheart" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 20098) (Disk XA78 318)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet with Hawaiian Guitars by Louise and Ferera, "On Honolulu Bay" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Sterling Trio, "In the Sweet Long Ago" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18212) (Disk XA78 315)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, Banjo by Fred Van Eps, "My Mammy" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Campbell, Albert and Henry Burr, "Underneath Hawaiian Skies" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18730) (Disk XA78 316)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Don't Take My Darling Boy Away" [] Side B: Peerless Quartet, "I'm On My Way to Dublin Bay " [] (Victor 17736-B) (Disk XA78 2337)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartet, "Somebody's Waiting For Someone" [] Side B: Burr, Henry, "Boys Who Won't Come Home" [] (Victor 18554-B) (Disk XA78 2432)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "For Your Country and My Country" [77053] Side B: Burr, Henry, "Joan of Arc" [77044] (Columbia A2273) (Disk XA78 2436)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "When Its Moonlight in Mayo" [45566] Side B: Stuart and Burton, "She Lives Down in Our Alley" [45568] (Columbia A1727) (Disk XA78 302)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "Makin's of the U.S.A." [77703] Side B: Peerless Quartette, "Keep the Trench Fires Going for the Boys Out There" [77704] (Columbia A2522) (Disk XA78 303)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "One and Two and Three and Four, Rock-A-Bye" [78303] Side B: Kaufman, Irving, "Chong" [78312] (Columbia A2714) (Disk XA78 310)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "There's a Typical Tipperary Over Here" [79061] Side B: Harrison, Charles, "That Old Irish Mother of Mine" [79085] (Columbia A2937) (Disk XA78 311)
  - Side A: Peerless Quartette, "Faugh-A-Ballah" [77656] Side B: Peerless Quartette and Arthur Fields, "Any Old Place the Gang Goes" [77617] (Columbia A2514) (Disk XA78 317)
  - Side A: Peers, Donald, "I Remember the Cornfields" [OEA.14816] Side B: Peers, Donald, "Among the Hills of Wales" [OEA.14817] (His Master's Voice I.P.605) (Disk XA78 321)
  - Side A: Perth and District Prize Pipe Band, "March, Strathspey, Reel" [M.14665] Side B: Perth and District Prize Pipe Band, "March, Strathspey, Reel" [M.14666] (Beltona BL.1987) (Disk XA78 322)
  - Side A: Pete Daley's Arkansas Fiddlers, "Lightning Express" [C 1147] Side B: Pete Daley's Arkansas Fiddlers, "Granny's Old Arm Chair" [C 1152] (Varsity 5078) (Disk XA78 954)
  - Side A: Peteler, Claire Lillian, "Face to Face" [6575] Side B: Peteler, Claire Lillian, "Last Rose of Summer" [6756] (Edison 80493) (Disk XA78 323)
  - Side A: Petersen, Joe, "Miner's Dream of Home" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Petersen, Joe, "Nellie Dean" [Matrix # not listed] (Rex 8923) (Disk XA78 324)
  - Side A: Petersen, Joe, "Good-Night Mum, Good-Night Dad" [R.2648] Side B: Petersen, Joe, "Rose Covered Shack" [R.2650] (Rex 9304) (Disk XA78 325)
  - Side A: Petersen, Joe, "Tiny Sprig of Shamrock" [R.2208] Side B: Petersen, Joe, "In an Old-Fashioned Town" [R.2345] (Rex 9265) (Disk XA78 326)
  - Side A: Peterson, Walter, "On a Sunday Afternoon; Just One Girl" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Peterson, Walter, "My Wild Irish Rose; My Irish Molly O" [Matrix # not listed] (Supertone 9197) (Disk XA78 1901)
  - Side A: Philadelphia Chamber String Simfonietta, "Londonderry Air" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Philadelphia Chamber String Simfonietta, "Gossips" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 4186) (Disk XA78 327)
  - Side A: Pipe Band of the 2nd Battn. (Queen's Own) Cameron Highlanders, "Inverness – Selection" [8439] Side B: Pipe Band of the 2nd Battn. (Queen's Own) Cameron Highlanders, "Popular Airs" [4521] (His Master's Voice B.3250) (Disk XA78 330)
  - Side A: Pipe Band of the 2nd Battn. (Queen's Own) Cameron Highlanders, "Retreat" [30-2012] Side B: Pipe Band of the 2nd Battn. (Queen's Own) Cameron Highlanders, "Retreat" [30-2013] (His Master's Voice B.3461) (Disk XA78 331)
  - Side A: Pipers of the 2nd Batt. Gordon Highlanders, "Brig o' Doon" [30-10765] Side B: Pipers of the 2nd Batt. Gordon Highlanders, "Soldier's Return" [30-10766] (His Master's Voice B.8085) (Disk XA78 1738)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "Flooers of the Forest; Lochaber No More" [M994A] Side B: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "Highland Cradle Song; The Green Hills of Tyroll" [M995B] (Beltona BL.2466) (Disk XA78 338)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "Skye Boat Sone" [M.986] Side B: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "King George V's Army" [M.987B] (Beltona BL.2465) (Disk XA78 1736)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "Road to the Isles" [OEA.980] Side B: Pipes and Drums – Scots Guards, "Back O' Benachie" [OEA.981] (Beltona BL.2461) (Disk XA78 1737)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Q.O. Cameron Highlanders, "Aldershot Command Searchlight Tattoo" [OEA.982] Side B: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Q.O. Cameron Highlanders, "Aldershot Command Searchlight Tattoo" [OEA.983] (His Master's Voice B.4447) (Disk XA78 561)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Scots Guards, "Highland Schottische" [M.994A] Side B: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Scots Guards, "Eightsome Reel" [M.995B] (His Master's Voice B.8344) (Disk XA78 1735)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Scots Guards, "Mallorca" [M990A] Side B: Pipes and Drums of the 2nd Batt. Scots Guards, "Dr. McCleods of Alnwick" [M991B] (His Master's Voice B.8292) (Disk XA78 1739)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "Road to the Isles" [M992A] Side B: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "Back O'Benachie-March" [M993B] (Beltona BL.2461) (Disk XA78 332)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "Shean Trubhais" [30-2002] Side B: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "Leaving St. Hilda " [30-2003] (Beltona BL.2464) (Disk XA78 333)
  - Side A: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "Skye Boat Song " [M990A] Side B: Pipes and Drums: Scots Guards, "King George V's Army" [M991B] (Beltona BL.2465) (Disk XA78 334)
  - Side A: Plantation Singers, "Swanee River" [30-11438] Side B: Plantation Singers, "Oh! Susannah" [30-11439] (Varsity 8142) (Disk XA78 1983)
  - Side A: Ben Pollack's Pisck a Rib Boys, "My Wild Irish Rose" [DLA 912] Side B: Daniels, Joe, "Drummer Goes to Town" [CE 7765] (Decca 3686) (Disk XA78 2696)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve and Ada Jones, "Christmas Morning at Clancy's" [77285] Side B: Prince's Band, "Hip, Hi Galop" [77360] (Columbia A2402) (Disk XA78 2302)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan at the Barber's" [596-2] Side B: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan's Real Estate Deal" [Matrix # not listed] (Grey Gull 4111) (Disk XA78 562)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Mrs. Dugan's Discovery" [46199] Side B: Casey, Michael, "Casey as a Judge" [29832] (Columbia A1940) (Disk XA78 1249)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Laughing Spectator" [3720] Side B: Jones, Ada and Len Spencer, "Bronco Bob and His Little Cheyenne" [3745] (Standard A432) (Disk XA78 1727)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan in a Broadway Car [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2448)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flannagan at the Doctors" [DLA 915] Side B: Campbell, Albert, "School Days" [DLA 912] (Standard A425) (Disk XA78 1728)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan at the Vocal Teacher's" [2178] Side B: Porter, Steve and Ernest Hare, "Arkansas Traveler" [2170] (Grey Gull 4112) (Disk XA78 1729)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan's Ocean Voyage" [8967] Side B: Herbert, Mr. Clarke and Miss Josephine De Butts, "Cohan's Pet Names" [3968] (Columbia A626) (Disk XA78 1730)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Laughing Spectator " [Matrix # not listed] (American 31229) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1732)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Backyard Conversation Between Two Irish Washer-women " [Matrix # not listed] (Leeds Records 4060) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1733)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Christmas Morning at Clancey's" [3773] Side B: Porter, Steve, "Clancey's Wooden Wedding" [3734] (Victor 16936) (Disk XA78 1984)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve, "Flanagan on a Broadway Car Talking" [3621] Side B: Vocal Quartette, "Suwanee River" [818] (Harmony Disc A368) (Disk XA78 2426)
  - Side A: Porter, Steve and Bill Murray, "Evening at Mrs. Clancey's Boarding House" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Stewart, Cal, "County Fair at Pumpkin Center" [Matrix # not listed] (Columbia A608) (Disk XA78 1731)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny, "If the Rest of the World Were Like Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny, "Medley in 6/8 Time" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-175) (Disk XA78 565)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny, "Medley of Irish Polkas" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny, "Medley of Highlands" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-177) (Disk XA78 566)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny, "Medley of Irish Jigs" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny, "Siege of Ennis No. 3" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-178) (Disk XA78 567)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny, "Donnybrook Fair" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny, "TK Polka" [Matrix # not listed] (Irish I-3003) (Disk XA78 568)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny, "Galway Bay" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny, "Colleen Bawn" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-121) (Disk XA78 1985)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny and His Irish Band of the Year, "Take This Message to My Mother and If I Were a Blackbird" [2176] Side B: Powell, Johnny and His Irish Band of the Year, "Greencastle and Dunphy's HornPipes" [2177] (Copley 9-120) (Disk XA78 563)
  - Side A: Powell, Johnny and His Irish Band of the Year, "Kevin Barry and Bold Jack Donohue" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powell, Johnny and His Irish Band of the Year, "Little Burnt Potato and the Bandon Blarney Stone" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-123) (Disk XA78 564)
  - Side A: Powell, Maud, "Spanish Dance" [] Side B: Powell, Maud, "St. Patrick's Day" [] (Victrola 6254-B) (Disk XA78 2327)
  - Side A: Powell, Maud, "Molly on the Shore" [One-sided] Side B: [] (Victor 64611) (Disk XA78 2700)
  - Side A: Powers, Jack, "Did Anyone Ever Tell You Mrs. Murphy" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Powers, Jack, "There They Are" [Matrix # not listed] (Regent 172) (Disk XA78 569)
  - Side A: Primrose, William and Sidonie Goossens, "Ave Maria" [CAX.7666] Side B: Primrose, William and Sidonie Goossens, "Londonderry Air" [CAX.7667] (Columbia 7378-M) 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2254)
  - Side A: Prince's Band, "Boy and the Birds" [77573] Side B: Burr, Henry, "In the Valley of Sunshine and Roses" [77581] (Columbia A2494) (Disk XA78 1225)
  - Side A: Prince's Band, "King Chanticleer" [19788] Side B: Harlan, Byron G., "They Gotta Quit Kickin' My Dawg Aroun'" [19791] (Columbia A1150) (Disk XA78 1725)
  - Side A: Prince's Dance Orchestra, "Mohammed" [78948] Side B: Prince's Dance Orchestra, "Afganistan" [78949] (Columbia A2883) (Disk XA78 2138)
  - Side A: Prince's Orchestra, "Miss McLeod's Reel" [39145] Side B: Prince's Orchestra, "Irish Washerwoman" [39146] (Columbia 33047-F) (Disk XA78 1724)
  - Side A: Prince's Orchestra, "Miss McLeod's Reel" [39145] Side B: Prince's Orchestra, "Irish Washerwoman" [39146] (Columbia A1474) (Disk XA78 1986)
  - Side A: Pryor's Orchestra, "Bit o' Blarney " [131332] (Columbia 3773) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1721)
  - Side A: Purcell, Noel, "Man Me Mother Married" [OEP.142] Side B: Purcell, Noel, "Dublin Saunter" [OEP.147] (Glenside W.125) (Disk XA78 1719)
  - Side A: Quinn, Dan, "Mick That Threw the Brick" [One-sided]" (Victor A-17) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2660)
  - Side A: Quinn, Dan, "Mrs. Mulligan, the Pride of the Coombe" [CAR.1234] Side B: Quinn, Dan, "Kevin Barry, Ireland's Boy Hero" [CAR.1237] (Regal Zonophone IZ.197) (Disk XA78 1717)
  - Side A: Quinn, Dan, "Foggy Dew " [CAR.3407] Side B: Quinn, Dan, "Bold Fenian Men" [CAR.3408] (Regal Zonophone IZ.295) (Disk XA78 1718)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Cup of Tea" [110274] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Rocky Road to Dublin" [110376] (Columbia 33348-F) (Disk XA78 571)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "McSorley's Twins" [143352] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Goodbye Mike, Goodbye Pat" [143353] (Regal G 9183) (Disk XA78 573)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Emerald Medley" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Eddie Dunn's Favorite Reel" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 79134) (Disk XA78 574)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Casey at the Party" [69877] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Bowl of Coffee" [69878] (Perfect 11094) (Disk XA78 1708)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Lassie from Donegal" [111134] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Home I Left Behind" [111135] (Okeh 84032) (Disk XA78 1709)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Old Bog Hole" [105917] Side B: Quinn, Frank and Kitty Hand, "Murphy's Wife" [105918] (Columbia 33064-F) (Disk XA78 1710)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Molly Durkin" [110814] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Halfpenny Reel" [110815] (Columbia 33355-F) (Disk XA78 1713)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank, "Tony and the Cop Part I" [112539] Side B: Quinn, Frank, "Court Scene, Part II" [112540] (Columbia 33449-F) (Disk XA78 1716)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank and Joe Maguire with Ed Gagan, "Clockin' Hen and Duck" [108599] Side B: Quinn, Frank and Joe Maguire with Ed Gagan, "Mist on the Mountain" [108601] (Columbia 33229-F) (Disk XA78 1712)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "Barney McCoy" [113139] Side B: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "My Blackbird of Sweet Avondale" [113310] (Regal Zonophone IZ.1070) (Disk XA78 1707)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "Daisy Bell" [112312] Side B: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "I'll Forgive But I'll Never Forget" [112313] (Columbia 33438-F) (Disk XA78 1714)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "One Night I Came Home" [112314] Side B: Quinn, Frank and Nan Fitzpatrick, "Going to the Fair" [112315] (Columbia 33443-F) (Disk XA78 1715)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank with Ed Gagan, "Connaught Man's Ramble" [109777] Side B: Quinn, Frank with Ed Gagan, "My Irish Molly O" [110155] (Okeh 84139) (Disk XA78 572)
  - Side A: Quinn, Frank with Ed Gagan, "Paddy McGinty's Goat" [107343] Side B: Quinn, Frank with Ed Gagan, "If You Are Irish Come Into the Parlor" [107344] (Columbia 33117-F) (Disk XA78 1711)
  - Side A: Quinn, William and His Dublin Orchestra, "Moonlight in Mayo" [W.113429] Side B: Quinn, William and His Dublin Orchestra, "Toss the Feathers" [W.113508] (Regal Zonophone IZ.208) (Disk XA78 1706)
  - Side A: Rabbett, Murty and His Gaelic Band, "Versouviana Dance" [9-107] Side B: Rabbett, Murty and His Gaelic Band, "Tickling Mary Jane" [9-106] (O'Byrne De Witt 9-105) (Disk XA78 1705)
  - Side A: Redmond, Michael and Marty Perry, "Blackbird" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Kimmel, John J., "Medley of Irish Reels No. 8" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18998) (Disk XA78 1704)
  - Side A: Redmond, Norman O'Connell, "Irish Emigrant" [F.2414A] Side B: Redmond, Norman O'Connell, "I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen" [F.2414B] (Decca GB.2975) (Disk XA78 1253)
  - Side A: Redmond, Norman O'Connell, "My Wild Irish Rose" [GB.2969] Side B: Redmond, Norman O'Connell, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [GB.2973] (Decca F.2410) (Disk XA78 1259)
  - Side A: Reed and Harrison, "My Little Dream Girl" [39983] Side B: Stuart and Burton, "I'm on My Way to Dublin Bay" [39987] (Cort Record F829) (Disk XA78 1248)
  - Side A: Reed, Phil, "Irish Jig Medley" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Reed, Phil, "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [Matrix # not listed] (Dance Tone 1137) (Disk XA78 575)
  - Side A: Reed, Susan, "Black Is the Color of My True Love's Hair" [M 1107] Side B: Reed, Susan, "I'm Sad and I'm Lonely " [M 1107] (RCA Victor 10-1280) (Disk XA78 1703)